One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
The
Wasp's
Nest
Pirate
Island
Hey, ya hear that?
If the world sank into the sea
a long time ago, wouldn’t that mean...
there’s treasure scattered
on the sea floor all over the world?!
You dumbass! That don’t mean
the entire world was a City of Gold!
Still! There’s gotta be some treasure
down there, for sure!
Use your head! Even if there is,
it’s 200 meters under water!
How d’ya even go that deep?!
We’d be gobbled up whole
by Sea Beasts.
Well, I hear tell there’s ships out there
that can dive deep into the ocean.
Sure, and ya think we have
the means to buy one?! Hell no!
Yeah, I guess it’d be easier
just to make friends with a Mermaid!
Mermaids! I’d love to meet one!
Grand
Line
Long before the time of Noland,
Saruyama Alliance Pirates - Last Boss
Montblanc Cricket
a kingdom with an advanced civilization
sank into the sea, huh?
Helluva story!
Masira, Shojo!
Wanna go diving again?
Now, this is what dreams are made of!
We’d follow you anywhere, Pops!
New
World
Ring, ring, ring...
Clik.
Tashigi.
Smoker.
Where are you now?
I’m at GS General Hospital.
Marine
GS General
Hospital
Koby...
So that means the One Piece is...
Yeah, this is a lot to take in...
I’m feeling lightheaded.
I’d better write it down later
to try and sort it out...
My brain can’t keep up.
Focus on healing up first.
Get involved now,
and you’ll just hold the rest of us back.
How’d it go?
The Captain’s making
a good recovery as well.
Good to hear.
But he wanted to be alone.
I see...
Prince...
If what Vegapunk is saying is true,
wouldn’t this lead to a grave conclusion?
It would.
Looks like this’ll lead
to some seriously awful answers.
In that case...
it’s time for us, SWORD, to step in!
Marine HQ Special Ops
SWORD Captain
X Drake
I know that my information is fragmented,
but providing the complete story
would require me to add speculation.
Just tell us!
What did Roger leave behind after
learning all about the Void Century, then?!
Labophase
Egghead
Look! The barrier’s been deactivated!
Ooh! Now we can get the hell outta here!
Now, what was that crash we heard earlier?
Scared the crap outta me!
Seems like the clouds stopped stretching.
It’s long enough now.
I think we can reach the sea.
But...
looks like a ton of ships have gathered
around our splashdown point.
Cola barrels in place!
You can eject anytime!
Okay!
Jinbe, not here yet?!
We’re almost there, but...
right now...
we’re following some kind of
mystery monster!
What?!
Hey, what’s with the detour?!
Come straight here—
This is no detour!
The monster’s coming your way!
Watch out!
Huh?!
A truly overwhelming presence
it’s got, indeed!
The Five Elders?!
Whaaa?!
Jinbe!
Got ya!
Fishman Jujutsu:
Piggyback!
Two-Sword Style:
Restful Paradise...
Rashomon!
– Kitetsu?!
Whoa!
Zoro!
Get the ship moving!
We’ll just hop on!
Do it now,
while you got the chance!
North-
Eastern
coast
Egghead
Straw Hat! You’re still not here?!
Hurry! Even this ship
can’t hold out against this!
It’s just one ship!
Forget the legends!
Send that ancient Elbaph ship
to the bottom of the ocean!
How long are you gonna
keep us waiting, Luffy?!
He’s out of our signal range, isn’t he?
Luffy!
Yeah!
We’re almost there! Get the ship moving!
I can’t believe shouting worked...
Get over here already!
Yeah! We’ll be there soon!
That’s our ship!
Woohoo!
Can’t wait to climb aboard!
Oimo, Kashi!
That’s...
The Captains!
Get the ship moving!
You got it, Captain!
Set sail!
Turn her about!
Don’t let them get away!
Don’t back down!
They’re just some pirate fossils
from a hundred years ago!
Shake ‘em off our tail...
ye boys!
Hey! Don’t give up! Keep fighting!
We can’t handle them!
Abandon posts!
All ships, form up on me!
I want an all-out assault!
Just pathetic!
Ain’t y’all gonna make
a stand for justice?!
Act like the heroes you are,
not a bunch of scrubs!
Vice Admiral Bluegrass!
Whoa! That put a hole in the ship!
I’ll put one in you too!
Rock-n-Roll...
Blaster!
Whoa! Vice Admiral Doll!
Love a good brawler!
Kashi!
Keep it up! So what
if they’re giants?!
Huh?
That boar ain’t after us no more!
Where’d it go?
That’s a good thing! Means all we
gotta do now is hop on the ship and...
Yup! And sail away!
In closing,
I want to deliver a single message:
Look! That must be...
Yes... The very same iron giant...
that attacked Mary Geoise
200 years ago.
There is no mistaking it!
To those scattered across the world...
...who bear the name of “D”!
Ace... Luffy...
Luffy... Vice Admiral Garp!
Captain!
Damn you!
Within each and every one of you...
lies—
That is quite enough out of you...
Vegapunk!
It cut out!
What was he going to say?!
What did he mean by “D”?!
Signal jamming?
Right at the crucial moment, too!
Damn it all!
It stopped...
Abandon ship!
What the hell’s with
that iron monster?!
The ship’s gonna go under!
that name...
Where are you?
Joyboy...
Where did you go?
I want to see you...
You were just here, right?
Joyboy...
That’s strange...
So very strange...
The Most Free
Technical issues?
He was still talking!
What could have caused
the transmission to stop?
And why did Vegapunk die
in the first place?
Someone assassinated him, maybe?
He said he’d committed crimes...
Maybe he was taken out
by the World Government?
Well, Straw Hat Luffy was
holding him hostage in the first place!
He’s a pirate!
He’s got to be the one to blame!
No matter what crimes
he committed,
there’s no way the Government
would kill the world’s greatest genius!
Den it must’ve been Luffyland...
Not a chance!
What the hell is that?!
A boar?! Or a mammoth?!
Wha?!
What’s going on in Egghead?!
York.
York!
Huh? What is it?
How many of the Vegapunks
are still alive?
The Vegapunks... Me and...
The number of people
accessing Punk Records right now...
is two!
Lilith is on this floor!
And Atlas is on the northeast coast!
Well done.
Shall we erase them all?
Yes.
Even after Stella’s death,
Punk Records was designed
to continue growing.
York’s development is beneficial for us,
but we have no need for other geniuses!
Go on, Stussy.
You “know full well what I’ll do next”, right?
We were friends?
Don’t make me laugh.
If anything, I respected you
as a ruthless colleague.
But once Lucci gets here,
I won’t be able to stop him!
Hey, Kaku. I...
Go!
Set sail!
We’re gettin’ outta here!
Aye!
All right! Hop aboard!
Yeaaah!
It’s the Captains!
Here he comes.
Luffy!
You’re all right!
O’ course we are!
It’s the Giants’ ship!
It’s so huge!
Isn’t Usopp here yet?
What about Chopper?
Nope, they’re still up there.
Thanks for bringin’ Luffy!
Got your ass kicked, huh, Kashi?
Oimo, Kashi!
Straw Hat!
Good to see you, man!
Yeah! Hey, got somethin’ to eat?
Dammit... After ‘em!
Don’t let ‘em get away!
We’ve plenty o’ warships!
The Giants are too powerful...!
Are you okay?!
Vice Admiral Doll!
Vice Admiral Bluegrass!
I hate being so powerless...
That’s some ability!
Damn you, Bonney!
You’ll be in real big trouble
if you let me get away, right, Marines?
Fire!
Sanji here, we just set sail.
Nami, how’s things up there?
We’re about to leave, too!
Thanks to Edison,
we should be able to reach the sea,
but please try to help us
if it looks like we won’t reach the water!
Nooo!
Of course!
Nami, Robin, Lilith...
I’ll rescue you,
even if all the other guys drown!
Rescue everyone!
I'll keep the ship safe!
Save us with it!
Something’s coming
from the center of the island!
It figures they wouldn’t give up yet...
The Five Elders.
Oh! My, now... You must be
Straw Hat Luffy, then?
The Captains did tell me to prepare
a lot of food because you’re a big eater.
I was gonna serve this
to you guys later.
Sorry!
I need dis now.
Can you make ‘nother one o’ dese?
You sure got a big appetite!
Dammit, he’s gonna catch up to us!
We gotta fight!
Protect the puny humans!
That’s hot!
Are you okay, Bjørn, Sig?!
You saved us! We owe you one!
Put out the fire!
Keep the fire away from the sails!
I wanna get Daddy and Vegapunk
somewhere else! We’ll be roasted alive here!
Let me...!
Guess we really can’t just
ignore those monsters.
Not when one of ‘em can fly!
It’ll follow us anywhere we go!
Here comes another one!
There’s that sound again...
All right! I’m full!
We’re countin’ on you, Luffy!
Uh?! Is this what he was
just talking about?
The sea level’s already rising?!
Holy crap!
Here we go!
Let the rhythm move you!
Hey! It’s a festival rhythm!
You idiot, quit dancing
and put out the fire!
Same to you!
Bonney!
Nika?!
Like I keep askin’, who’s that?
Let’s go. You wanna beat those
guys up, don’t you?
That’s impossible for me!
‘Cause I’m not like you...
You can do it!
Don’t got a clue how
your ability works, though!
That’s just how I look when I’m free!
What’s that?!
Distortion Future!
Future Where...
...I’m the Most Free!
Now you’re gettin’ it, Bonney!
Don’t worry, Ginny...
I’ll raise your daughter.
I did it!
Yeah!
There’s two Nikas!
Who are they?!
White Giants?!
I sense a peculiar presence...
Let us hurry.
Let’s go!
Yeah!
There...!
Now things’re gettin’ fun!
That’s the face on
Straw Hat Luffy’s wanted poster!
Nika!
Two Nikas?
A mere illusion,
created by the Age-Age Fruit!
Do not tempt fate!
Luffy! Stop that Elder!
I got this!
Nika!
Listen up, boys!
Shreddin’ ‘em or crushin’ ‘em
won’t do nothin’ to ‘em!
Huh?! So what’re you doing, then?!
So...
I want you all to hit me
as hard as you can!
You’re telling me the only option’s
to send them flying?!
Got it! As hard as I can, right?!
What?! We’re gonna hit Luffy?!
Why?!
We’re counting on you, guys!
Take care of the bird!
Put out the fire and get us sailin’ again!
And quit dancing, you morons!
Huh?!
But you were doing it too!
What are you doing?! Release me!
Hurry up!
What?!
You’re really gonna hit him?!
Captain’s orders, Bonney!
Ifrit Jambe:
Strong Impact...
Don’t keep wafflin’ about it, Bonney!
Hit me as hard as you can!
All right then...
Super-Size...
Hell Memories!
Right!
Nika Punch!
That hurts!
What?! We’re hurting you?!
Of course you are...
because y’all are using Haki!
Gum-Gum...
Don’t lose your grip, Bonney!
Push hard, like yer tryin’
to squeeze the life outta him!
What is up with you guys?!
Dawn...
Balloon!
All right, away it goes!
And it ain’t never comin’ back!
We did it!
Let’s get goin’, people!
So, where’s Usopp and the others?
They were supposed to be
on their way down by now...
They’re takin’ forever...
Something might’ve happened up there.
Huh? Atlas...
I’ll go check!
Wait, Atlas!
York is monitoring both of us...
Lilith, we’re...
...nothing...
It’s back!
What?! It’s back on!
...inherited through the generations...
...can be called a will...
What’s he talking about?
It came back on!
Was it just bad reception?
So you just cut off
the Mental Waves temporarily!
A Transmission Transponder Snail’s memory
and Mental Waves’re on separate circuits!
Yous gotta destroy
the actual thing, Elders!
I pray this message will surely find...
those at the mercy of this reason.
Guh?! Why?!
Rain? A bombardment?!
No!
It’s a bunch of rubble
and Cipher Pol agents!
Why are they falling from the sky?!
Catch them! Or they’re gonna die!
Seraphim are with them, too!
Hey, old guy! That monster’s
the one spittin’ them out!
Looks like a fountain!
It’s gonna come this way!
Hurry up and get away from it!
Huh, this again?!
Here it comes!
It’s inhalin’ us! Get us outta here!
We’re bein’ pulled back!
I can’t keep going...
Freedom’s exhausting...
Bonney?!
Furl the sails! Use the oars!
Ya big jerk...!
Naptime for you, pal!
Get ‘em, Nika!
White Giants! Monsters!
Cipher Pol falling from the sky!
Have I been dreaming the whole time?!
Oh, crap!
The boar’s headed your way!
Watch out!
That thing’s super tough!
Not that one!
He’ll smash the ship to pieces!
We gotta flee!
Joyboy!
Got that, Emet?
Only when the time is right.
Time is right?
What the hell is that?!
Robooo!
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
piipapii papipo, piipapii
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
no no no no no norenai
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama feel so good, mata unlucky demo
cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no boys & girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no boys & girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran run run run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga punk!!!!!! no way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamine
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru